{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Christmas Light Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46334/":{"taskOID":46334,"originalTaskOID":46334,"setID":1026,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501924,"questionDisplayText":"Will you provide lights?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will you be providing the holiday lights?","shortQuestionText":"Will you be providing the holiday lights?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200201,"questionDisplayText":"Decorative Elements Desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What decorative elements will be included?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17406,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bushes ","answerDisplayText":"Bushes ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17408,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greenery / Wreaths","answerDisplayText":"Greenery / Wreaths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Groundlighting","answerDisplayText":"Groundlighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17407,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Motifs","answerDisplayText":"Motifs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501924,"questionDisplayText":"Will you provide lights?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will you be providing the holiday lights?","shortQuestionText":"Will you be providing the holiday lights?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200201,"questionDisplayText":"Decorative Elements Desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What decorative elements will be included?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17406,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bushes ","answerDisplayText":"Bushes ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17408,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greenery / Wreaths","answerDisplayText":"Greenery / Wreaths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Groundlighting","answerDisplayText":"Groundlighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17407,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Motifs","answerDisplayText":"Motifs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6491,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Trees","answerDisplayText":"Trees","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17406,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bushes ","answerDisplayText":"Bushes ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17408,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greenery / Wreaths","answerDisplayText":"Greenery / Wreaths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Groundlighting","answerDisplayText":"Groundlighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17407,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Motifs","answerDisplayText":"Motifs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/46334/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46334,"taskName":"Holiday Lighting - Add or Remove","taskDescription":"Add or Remove Holiday Lighting","xmTaskDescriptor":"Christmas Light Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":119,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Holiday outdoor lights Lighting lawn","textMessagingName":"Holiday Lights","rolloverLongDesc":"Temporary holiday lighting for exterior, grounds and interior","rolloverShortDesc":"Temporary holiday lighting for exterior, grounds and interior","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Add Holiday Lighting.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Install Christmas Lights \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Holiday Lighting Installation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Holiday Lighting - Add or Remove","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Holiday Lighting - Add or Remove - Materials Not Provided by Homeowner","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Holiday Lighting Project","urlName":"Holiday-Lighting-Add-or-Remove","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"Best Christmas Light Installation \u003cin_city\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Hang Holiday Lighting","searchKeywords":"Holiday,outdoor,lights,Lighting,lawn,display,christmas,decoration,icicle,twinkle,Ornament,Decor","emcCategoryOid":-12046,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1026,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}